# Iryna Loushkina

Junior Front end Developer (React)

### Profile

8+ years experience in many different projects, starting from sales / account management, implementation online booking tools to managing people.

Starting January 2020 I've been studying how to create responsive websites / small SPAs and environment connected to that process. I can deploy and maintain small projects so far.

What I mean by that? I can build websites for individuals and small business, create mobile-friendly layouts and CSS animations /effects, add dynamic page functionality, build small client-side apps with JavaScript etc.

You are more than welcome to visit my portfolio and GitHub

https://iloush.github.io/irina\_loushkina\_cv/

https://github.com/iLoush

# Employment History

Junior Frontend Developer at QTdata, Tallinn

February 2020 — Present

- Fix small bags
- Update layouts

Account Manager at Booking.com, Kiev

July 2017 — October 2019

Account Manager at American Express GBT, Kiev

November 2015 — July 2017

## Education

Bachelor degree of Economy, National Aviation Univesity, Ukraine

September 2007 — May 2011

#### Courses

JavaScript for beginners, Udemy

May 2020

Advanced CSS and SASS: flexbox, grid and animations, Udemy

June 2020

PHP for beginners. Part 1, Udemy

July 2020

PHP for beginners. Part 2 - PDO, MySQL, phpMyAdmin, Udemy

July 2020

#### **Details**

Amsterdam, +31 6 12 96 30 71 iloushkina@gmail.com

#### Links

Linkedin Portfolio GitHub

#### **Skills**

HTML5

CSS3

SASS (SCSS syntax)

familiar with Bootstrap /

**Tailwind** 

fundamentals of JavaScript

(ES6 +)

**j**Query

fundamentals of TypeScript

fundamentals of React

fundamentals of Vue.js

familiar with Axios

fundamentals of PHP

#### Languages

**English** 

Ukrainian | Russian

Dutch

#### **Hobbies**

Biking,

Running,

Traveling, Cooking